<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-22T15:54:57+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kris 👋</title><entry><title type="html">Test 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/test-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test 2" /><published>2018-12-13T21:21:13+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-13T21:21:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/test2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/test-2/">&lt;div&gt;
  test 2
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Conference" /><summary type="html">test 2</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/test.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Test 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/test-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test 1" /><published>2018-12-12T21:21:13+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-12T21:21:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/test1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/test-1/">&lt;div&gt;
  test 1
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Conference" /><category term="web" /><category term="mobile" /><category term="content" /><summary type="html">test 1</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/test.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Where did my time go?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/where-did-my-time-go/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where did my time go?" /><published>2018-12-12T21:21:13+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-12T21:21:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/where-did-my-time-go</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/where-did-my-time-go/">&lt;section&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;text-center my-4&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wheredidmytimego.netlify.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Visit Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Problem and Idea&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I wake up between 5-6am every morning. And I am trying to be as productive as possible over the next 3-4 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;But often happens that the morning is over, and I have the feeling that I have done nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In order to prevent this, I started to log every activity that I did on a notepad and the time that I did it in. When the morning was over, I could look at this log and inspect my activities&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I realised that I could build a product that simplifies this process a little bit&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;hr class=&quot;hr-w-25&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Design &amp; Build&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;Design&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I wanted to simply log my activities and categorise them as Productive or Unproductive.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Once done, I also wanted to view have a timeline where I could inspect all my activities in a nice and clear manner&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;Build&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I built the product livestreaming it on Twitch. This was a pretty cool experience, but still a bit stressful, as never before people have watched me code.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I would love to continue doing this in the future, but this time with commentary. It would be a good material for YouTube also, as it could show inspiring Software Developers what's coding really like.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Where did my time go was built using ReactJS, as this was the fastest solution for me&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;hr class=&quot;hr-w-25&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Ship&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As soon as I hit MVP stage, which took me about 5 hours of programming, I decided to stop working on it and share it to my Twitter account&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I have several additional features I plan to include in the near future:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Ability to edit Activities&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Drag and drop activities&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;More statistics in the Timeline page, e.g. Percentage of productive vs unproductive tasks; longest task&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="project" /><category term="web" /><category term="project" /><category term="productivity" /><summary type="html">Visit Website Problem and Idea I wake up between 5-6am every morning. And I am trying to be as productive as possible over the next 3-4 hours. But often happens that the morning is over, and I have the feeling that I have done nothing. In order to prevent this, I started to log every activity that I did on a notepad and the time that I did it in. When the morning was over, I could look at this log and inspect my activities I realised that I could build a product that simplifies this process a little bit Design &amp; Build Design I wanted to simply log my activities and categorise them as Productive or Unproductive. Once done, I also wanted to view have a timeline where I could inspect all my activities in a nice and clear manner Build I built the product livestreaming it on Twitch. This was a pretty cool experience, but still a bit stressful, as never before people have watched me code. I would love to continue doing this in the future, but this time with commentary. It would be a good material for YouTube also, as it could show inspiring Software Developers what's coding really like.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/where-did-my-time-go/main.jpg" /></entry></feed>